Name: Igor Tosic

Date of Birth: 24.07.1980

Email: igortosic1980@gmail.com

Mob: +4745832552



Profile:

I have 18 years working experience in different types of industry, such as Broadcast Media, IT/Computer and software, government and private sector and Digital Marketing. I am available to work in a variety of environments with modern technologies.

As the web developer, my focus is on developing CMS, UX, data analyst, converting, marketing automation, authentication and authorization, APIs.

- HTML5, CSS3
- JavaScript, React
- Python, Django
- Semantic UI, Bootstrap, Material Design
- Django CMS, Word Press, EVOQ
- Database MySQL/SQL and MongoDB
- Cloud: Heroku, DIVIO, GCloud
- Digital design, video production, advertising

Experience:

09.2016 - present Web developer at Sticos AS, Norway (www.sticos.no)

- · Web developing
- Working with Big Data, APIs and web personalization
- Marketing automation with Marketo
- DNN/EVOQ CMS
- Video production

07.2015 - 05.2016 Web developer at Plapre AS, Norway (www.plapre.com)

- Working on ICT and technical developing solutions
- Front-end and UX development
- Backend PHP developing
- Contribute to products development and improvement of existing products

04.2014 - 06.2015 Web developer and Multimedia designer - part time at Cyber Team, Serbia (www.cyberteam.rs)

- HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript
- digital design, video production, advertising, Google Ad Words,
- Word Press, SEO/SEM, Affiliate and Viral marketing, Website optimization
- IT strategy, e-commerce
- Visual communication
- PHP and MySQL
- Bootstrap, Foundation, Angular

10.2009 - 04.2014 Expert associate The Coordination Body the Government of the Republic Serbia for the Municipalities of Presevo, Bujanovac and Medvedja - http://www.kt.gov.rs/

- Video editing, post production and shooting
- · Graphics design, advertising
- On line promotion, workshop teaching

09.2005 - 06.2011 Founder and CTO of Agency Easymindstudio, Serbia- partnership with Cyberteam, Serbia igortosic.com, vimeo.com/igortosic, flickr.com/photos/igortosic/, www.youtube.com/user/igortosicvideo

- Video editing, post production and shooting
- · Graphics design, advertising
- SEO/SEM
- HTML, CSS

06.2004 - 09.2007 Database administrator and post production editor in TV Studio Valjevo (www.tvvaplus.rs)

- developing a database and implementing
- implementing the basic forms of data protection
- Video editing, post-production
- · Graphics design, advertising
- manage documents and keep them in different versions

11.2002 - 06.2004 Video editor and graphics designer in Radio Television Serbia for regional program

- · Graphics design, advertising
- Video editing, post production

11.2002 - 09.2012 TV B92, Belgrade, Serbia, videographer (part time) http://www.b92.net/

10.2000 - 10.2002 IT operator and videographer in TV Vujic, Serbiahttp://www.vtv.rs/

• Live TV programs, studio programs, editing video, network and live room operation

Education:

03.2017 - paused Udacity, Nanodegree - Full Stack Web Developer

10.2003 - 07.2009 High Business School of vocational studies (BA in Business IT), Valjevo, Serbia

11.2011 - 11.2012 IT Academy, Belgrade – Java Development (one-year course)

Portfolio:

Bitbucket: https://bitbucket.org/igortosic/

GitHub: https://github.com/igortosic-easymind

Gist: https://gist.github.com/igortosic-easymind

Websites (some of examples):

https://sticos.no/

http://spørkostra.no/

https://else.sticos.no/

http://www.contoregnskap.no/

https://plapre.no/

http://emagasin.carlsenfritzoe.no/

https://www.medox.no/

http://medox.se/

http://lunehjem.brodfabrikken.no/

http://cureberry.no/

https://k2vitamin.no/

http://ikuben.no/

http://emagasin.santanderkredittkort.no/

http://no.xylitol.com/

http://friskerelenger.no/

http://uro.sovnproblemer.no/